♪ 不要抱怨，抱我 ♪
♪ 最近有谣言说我喜欢你，我要澄清一下，那不是谣言. ♪
♪ 我怀疑你的本质是一本书，不然为什么让我越看越想睡 ♪
♪ 你知道我的缺点是什么吗？ 是缺点你. ♪
♪ 我发现昨天很喜欢你，今天也很喜欢你，而且有预感明天也会喜欢你。 ♪
♪ 近朱者赤，近你者甜. ♪
♪ 我是九你是三，除了你还是你. ♪
♪ 你知道你和星星有什么区别吗？星星在天上，你在我心里. ♪
♪ 这是我的手背，这是我的脚背，你是我的宝贝 ♪
♪ 猜猜我的心在哪边？左边，错了，在你那边. ♪
♪ 听闻先生治家有方，小女余生愿闻其详 ♪
♪ 你闻到什么味道了吗？没有啊，怎么你一出来空气都是甜的了. ♪
♪ 莫文蔚的阴天，孙燕姿的雨天周杰伦的晴天，都不如你和我聊天 ♪
♪ you see it getting closer. ♪
♪ Just surrender 'cause you ♪
♪ feel the feeling taking over. ♪
♪ It's fire, it's freedom, ♪
♪ it's flooding open. ♪
♪ It's a preacher in the pulpit ♪
♪ and you'll find devotion. ♪
♪ There's something breaking at the brick of ♪
♪ every wall it's holding all that you know, ♪
♪ so tell me do you wanna go? ♪
♪ Where it's covered in ♪
♪ all the colored lights. ♪
♪ Where the runaways ♪
♪ are running the night. ♪
♪ Impossible comes true, ♪
♪ it's taking over you. ♪
♪ Oh, this is the greatest show. ♪
♪ We light it up, we won't come down. ♪
♪ And the sun can't stop us now. ♪
♪ Watching it come true, ♪
♪ it's taking over you. ♪
♪ Oh, this is the greatest show. ♪
♪ It's everything you ever want. ♪
♪ It's everything you ever need. ♪
♪ And it's here right in front of you. ♪
♪ This is where you wanna be. ♪
♪ It's everything you ever want. ♪
♪ It's everything you ever need. ♪
♪ And it's here right in front of you. ♪
♪ This is where you wanna be. ♪
♪ It's everything you ever want ♪
♪ It's everything you ever need. ♪
♪ And it's here right in front of you. ♪
♪ This is where you wanna be. ♪
♪ It's everything you ever want. ♪
♪ It's everything you ever need. ♪
♪ And it's here right in front of you. ♪
I understand, yes. Thank you
very much, Mr. Jeffrey. Thank you.
You have the money
by the end of the day.
Let's go.
Phineas, hurry up. We are
gonna miss the train.
Stand up straight.
Wipe that muck off.
Keep up.
Arm extended, elbow out.
Sip, and never slurp.
Begin here, arm extended...
elbow out.
Keep your cup level.
Low your cup.
Shall we do it again?
Arm extended, elbow out.
Gracefully.
Charity, come here.
Your dress. Is this how we
have taught you to behave?
It's my fault, sir.
I made her laugh.
Well, thank you
for your honesty.
Stay away from my daughter.
- How did you get out?
- The window.
Father is sending me
to finishing school.
I don't know what my future will be.
I do.
♪ I close my eyes ♪
♪ and I can see. ♪
♪ The world that's ♪
♪ waiting up for me. ♪
♪ That I call my own. ♪
♪ Through the dark, ♪
♪ through the door ♪
♪ Through where no one's ♪
♪ been before ♪
♪ but it feels like home. ♪
♪ They can say, they can ♪
♪ say it all sounds crazy. ♪
♪ say I've lost my mind. ♪
♪ I don't care, I don't ♪
♪ care, so call me crazy. ♪
♪ We can live in a world ♪
♪ that we design ♪
♪ 'Cause every night I lie in bed. ♪
♪ The brightest colors ♪
♪ fill my head. ♪
♪ A million dreams are ♪
♪ keeping me awake. ♪
♪ I think of what ♪
♪ the world could be. ♪
♪ A vision of the one I see. ♪
♪ A million dreams is ♪
♪ all it's gonna take. ♪
♪ A million dreams for the ♪
♪ world we're gonna make. ♪
♪ They can say, they can ♪
♪ say it all sounds crazy. ♪
♪ say we've lost our minds. ♪
Charity!
♪ I don't care, I don't care ♪
♪ if they call us crazy. ♪
♪ run away to a world ♪
♪ that we designed. ♪
♪ Cause every night I lie in bed. ♪
♪ The brightest colors fill my head. ♪
♪ A million dreams are ♪
♪ keeping me awake. ♪
♪ I think of what ♪
♪ the world could be. ♪
♪ A vision of ♪
♪ the one I see. ♪
♪ A million dreams is ♪
♪ all it's gonna take. ♪
No.
♪ A million dreams for the ♪
♪ world we're gonna make. ♪
Newspapers. Amazing stories
from around the world.
♪ A million dreams are ♪
♪ keeping me awake. ♪
♪ I think of what the ♪
♪ world could be. ♪
♪ A vision of ♪
♪ the one I see. ♪
♪ A million dreams is ♪
♪ all it's gonna take. ♪
♪ A million dreams for the ♪
♪ world we're gonna make. ♪
Come join the
Great American Railroad.
Three meals a day. A roof over your head.
Fair and ample wages.
Come, make your fortune.
See the open plains of America.
Opportunity awaits you sir,
out on the rails.
Sir I, I know I don't
come from much
but I will take care
of your daughter
and I will give her a
life as grand as this one.
Goodbye, mother.
She'll be back.
Sooner or later she will get tired
of your life of having nothing
and she will keep
running back home.
♪ Every night I lie in bed. ♪
♪ The brightest colors fill my head. ♪
♪ A million dreams are ♪
♪ keeping me awake. ♪
♪ I think of what the ♪
♪ world could be. ♪
♪ A vision of the one I see. ♪
♪ A million dreams is all ♪
♪ it's gonna take. ♪
♪ A million dreams for the ♪
♪ world we're gonna make. ♪
♪ However big, ♪
♪ however small. ♪
♪ Let me be part of it all. ♪
♪ Share your dreams with me. ♪
♪ You may be right, ♪
♪ you may be wrong. ♪
♪ But say that ♪
♪ you'll bring me along. ♪
♪ To the world you see. ♪
♪ To the world I close ♪
♪ my eyes to see. ♪
♪ I close my eyes to see ♪
♪ Cause every night I lie in bed. ♪
♪ The brightest colors fill my head. ♪
♪ A million dreams are ♪
♪ keeping me awake. ♪
♪ A million dreams, ♪
♪ a million dreams. ♪
♪ I think of what the world could be. ♪
♪ A vision of what I see. ♪
♪ A million dreams is all ♪
♪ it's gonna take. ♪
♪ A million dreams for the ♪
♪ world we're gonna make. ♪
♪ For the world ♪
♪ we're gonna make. ♪
- Mr. Smith?
- Yeah.
Have a look at this, here?
Yes, yes, I see it.
Thank you, Chalmers,
that will do.
Sir. Phineas Taylor Barnum.
If I may sir,
I believe I have
skills and ideas...
that go well beyond counting
numbers into an adding machine.
I have read about this
German fellow, Lilienthal...
I believe he's developed a glider
that could take a
man in the air, sir.
Isn't that amazing?
I mean,
if you were to apply that to this business,
it would be revolutionary.
Gentlemen. Can I have your attention?
You are all dismissed.
Bankrupt?
I thought the company had
a dozen trading ships.
Yes, at the bottom of
the South China Seas.
A typhoon sank them all.
- Tinker it.
- Oh, you're in for it.
- Hey.
- Oh God. You are home early.
And until further notice.
Oh I didn't think you
were along for that job.
Or any job apparently.
That's what makes our life
together so exciting.
Charity.
- This isn't the life I promised you.
- But I have everything I want.
- What about the magic?
- What do you call those two girls?
Hey, you partners, look who.
Daddy!
- Come here.
- Did you bring a present?
Present, for what?
- For my birthday.
- Your what?
- My birthday.
- It's not your birthday.
Okay, I do have a present.
But not just any present.
Oh no.
The most amazing
birthday present ever.
This extraordinary machine was originally
created by Leonardo Da Vinci 400 years ago.
But the blueprints have
been lost for centuries,
until just last week,
on a stormy night...
when a sunken pirate ship washed
up on the shores of Nantucket.
They found skeletons and treasures...
and the blueprints were recovered
by none other than JW Mercantile.
The blueprints crossed
my desk very briefly...
but I managed to commit
them to memory...
and if I had remembered correctly...
Happy birthday, Caroline.
This is a wishing machine.
You tell it your wishes...
and it keeps them safe
until they come true.
Even if you forget them,
they are always there.
- Can I tell a wish?
- Step right up. Go ahead.
- I wish to marry Santa Clause.
- That is a good wish.
I wish for ballet slippers.
Hey, that's a good wish too.
What is your wish, Mommy?
I wish...
for happiness like this forever.
For you and you...
and for your father.
- Boring.
- Boring?
Since when is happiness
ever been boring?
♪ Every night I lie in bed. ♪
♪ The brightest colors fill my head. ♪
♪ A million dreams are ♪
♪ keeping me awake. ♪
♪ I think of what ♪
♪ the world could be. ♪
♪ A vision of the one I see. ♪
♪ A million dreams is all ♪
♪ it's gonna take. ♪
♪ A million dreams for the ♪
♪ world we're gonna make. ♪
The goat prices go up, so
the pork bellies go down.
- Charles, we're leaving.
- Huh?
This bank only wants to lend
money to people with money.
What are you looking at
Flop Doodle?
Mr. Barnum.
This venture you propose
is risky and somewhat bizarre.
It's a good bet, it's what it is.
Sir, people don't wanna admit it...
but they are fascinated with
the exotic and the...
is why we stare at it.
The bank is going to need
substantial collateral.
Of course. I would not
suggest otherwise.
The deed and title to my entire
fleet of trading vessels.
Why would a bank loan us 10,000 dollars?
Because we put up collateral.
We don't have any collateral.
Sure we do. In the
South China Seas.
- In the South China Seas?
- Deep in the South China Seas.
And what did we
buy with this loan?
Barnum's American Museum of Curiosity.
What kind of museum is it?
A place to be transported.
A place where people can see
thing they've never seen before.
- Wax figures?
- Yeah.
They are all the
rage in Europe. Look.
Marie Antoinette with the sore throat.
Napoleon. Come here.
You see?
You have already met some of the most
famous folks from the history.
But they are not all wax.
This is the Great O'Malley.
Master of sleight of hand,
the king of deception.
- You don't look like a magician.
- I am a thief.
A very good thief.
I caught him taking my watch.
- You see?
- An elephant.
Not just any elephant.
I'll get you something
real nice to say the word.
- Thank you.
- Oh yeah. This is a ten ton bulls...
straight from the plains of Africa.
And, look at that.
- The tallest giraffe in the world.
- Can I climb up its leg?
Absolutely no. OK.
- Now, I know how it looks.
- If you didn't, I would be worried.
I mean it just needs a little work..
The loan has to be paid
back every month.
Oh yeah, we're gonna pay.
We just need customers.
- Hundreds of them.
- We're gonna get them.
Welcome to the Barnum Museum.
It is one hour of your time, sir...
but it will change your life.
We have a shows on
the hour, every hour.
I love your dress.
Surely not for the fainted heart.
I can tell you that you'll love it.
Half the price for anyone
who is wearing a hat.
Ho ho, That's you, sir.
Welcome to the Barnum Museum.
Garbage.
Welcome to the Barnum Museum,
where everyone...
How many tickets?
- Three.
- Three?
Daddy.
Daddy?
- You sell anymore tickets today?
- A few. Yeah.
Most of 'em was
rushing home, it's Friday.
We sold a few.
I think you have too many dead
things in your museum daddy.
Do you?
She is right.
You need something alive.
- Go to sleep, both of you.
- Something sensational.
- That is a big word.
- That's your word.
Something that isn't stuffed.
- Like a mermaid.
- Or a unicorn.
- Unicorns aren't real.
- Well, mermaids aren't real either.
You must be Gertrude Stratton.
I am looking for your son.
I don't have a son.
The hospital record says you do.
Charles, right? Age 22?
Charles.
P. T Barnum.
At your service.
I'm putting together a show...
and I need a star.
You want people
to laugh at me.
Well, they are laughing anyway, kid.
So, might as well get paid.
I see a soldier.
No, a general...
riding across the stage
with a sword and gun and...
and the most beautiful
uniform ever made.
People will come from
all over the world
and when they see him
they won't laugh.
They will salute.
Wanted! Unique persons, curiosities.
Daring acts. Wonders of the world.
How is it looking girls?
Hey. You looking for freaks?
I know where you
can find one of them.
Really?
Come on, girls.
- Hello.
- Sir, you can't be here.
I'm sorry.
Who is doing that singing?
It's you, isn't it?
- Sir, I'll have to ask you to leave.
- You are so talented, blessed...
Extraordinary.
Unique.
I would even say 'beautiful'.
Sir,
please leave me alone.
They don't understand it,
but they will.
OK. Anne and WD Wheeler.
Brother and sister?
- Yes sir.
- Terrific. And what do you do?
- Trapeze.
- Trapeze. OK.
You know, people aren't gonna like
it if you put us on the stage.
Oh, I am counting on it.
- Is this so far your...
- Entire body.
Fantastic.
I don't need to see it.
Tattoo Man
Barnum Museum.
Dog boy.
Can I just ask how heavy you are?
Do you have a number for that?
- I prefer not to say it, but...
- Just between you and me.
500 pounds.
- 750 pounds? Is what you said?
- 750 pounds!
World's heaviest man.
- What's your name?
- Vasily Palvos, sir.
Yeah, we are going to change that name.
I think you're Irish.
Irish Giant.
We have a show.
That's good, but I need
it five times bigger.
And I want it everywhere.
Carriages, sides of trains,
trolleys, crates...
milk bottles,
everywhere they look.
Barnum's American Museum.
Nice to see you, sir.
♪ You stumble through your days. ♪
♪ Got your head hung low. ♪
♪ Your skies' a shade of Grey. ♪
♪ Like a zombie in a maze. ♪
♪ - Two, please. ♪
♪ You're asleep inside ♪
♪ But you can shake awake. ♪
♪ 'Cause you're just a dead man walking ♪
♪ Thinking that's your only option. ♪
♪ But you can flip the switch and ♪
♪ brighten up your darkest day. ♪
♪ Sun is up and the color's blinding. ♪
♪ Take the world and redefine it. ♪
♪ Leave behind your narrow mind. ♪
♪ You'll never be the same. ♪
♪ Come alive, come alive. ♪
♪ Go and light your light. ♪
♪ Let it burn so bright. ♪
♪ Reaching up ♪
♪ to the sky. ♪
♪ And it's open wide. ♪
♪ You're electrified. ♪
♪ When the world becomes a fantasy. ♪
♪ And you're more than ♪
♪ you could ever be. ♪
♪ 'Cause you're dreaming ♪
♪ with your eyes wide open. ♪
♪ And you know ♪
♪ you can't go back again. ♪
♪ To the world that ♪
♪ you were living in. ♪
♪ 'Cause you're dreaming ♪
♪ with your eyes wide open. ♪
♪ So, come alive! ♪
- Lettie. They are waiting.
- For what?
- For you.
- No.
They don't know it yet,
but they are gonna love you.
Trust me.
Tom.
Up, up.
♪ I see it in your eyes. ♪
♪ You believe that lie. ♪
♪ That you need to hide your face. ♪
♪ Afraid to go outside. ♪
♪ So you lock the door. ♪
♪ But don't you stay that way. ♪
♪ No more living in those shadows. ♪
♪ You and me, we know how that goes. ♪
♪ 'Cause once you see it, oh ♪
♪ you'll never, never be the same. ♪
♪ We will be the light that's turning. ♪
♪ Bottle up but keep on shining. ♪
♪ You can prove there's more to you. ♪
♪ You cannot be afraid. ♪
♪ Come alive, come alive. ♪
♪ Go and light your light. ♪
♪ Let it burn so bright. ♪
♪ Reaching up to the sky. ♪
♪ And it's open wide. ♪
♪ You're electrified. ♪
♪ When the world becomes a fantasy. ♪
♪ And you're more than ♪
♪ you could ever be. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're dreaming ♪
♪ with our eyes wide open. ♪
♪ And we know we can't go back again. ♪
♪ To the world that we were living in. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're dreaming ♪
♪ with our eyes wide open. ♪
♪ So, come alive! ♪
Bravo.
That was amazing.
- Superb!
- Fantastic.
This is bad. The Barnum Museum. A
primitive Circus of Humbug.
"Criminal." "Greedy".
"A circus."
I like circus.
That's right, bad boy.
You are gonna protect
the bearded lady?
Hay... That's enough.
Walter.
- Inside, all! Right?
- Look them run.
- We do not want your kind here.
- Get out of here.
That's right, you freaks.
Your master's calling.
That's quite enough, sir.
Nothing more to look at.
At your service.
You print this review in
every paper in New York.
Half price ticket to
anyone who with it.
Sold out.
♪ Come one! ♪
♪ Come all! ♪
♪ Come in! ♪
♪ Come on! ♪
♪ To anyone who's ♪
♪ bursting with a dream. ♪
♪ Come one! ♪
♪ Come all! ♪
♪ You hear the call. ♪
♪ To anyone who's searching ♪
♪ for a way to break free. ♪
♪ Break free! ♪
♪ When the world becomes a fantasy. ♪
♪ And you're more than ♪
♪ you could ever be. ♪
♪ 'Cause you're dreaming ♪
♪ with your eyes wide open. ♪
♪ And we know we ♪
♪ can't go back again. ♪
♪ To the world that we were living in. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're dreaming ♪
♪ with our eyes wide open. ♪
♪ When the world becomes a fantasy. ♪
♪ And you're more than ♪
♪ you could ever be. ♪
♪ 'Cause you're dreaming ♪
♪ with your eyes wide open. ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah. ♪
♪ And we know we ♪
♪ can't go back again. ♪
♪ To the world that we were living in. ♪
♪ 'Cause we're dreaming ♪
♪ with our eyes wide open. ♪
♪ So come alive! ♪
♪ Come alive. ♪
Peanuts.
Get your peanuts here.
- Hot, salted peanuts.
- One for me and one for the lady.
O'Malley.
Ah, Mr. Bennett from the Herald.
Come to take in
another show, huh?
Tell me, Mr. Barnum,
does it bother you
that everything you're selling is fake?
Do these smiles seem fake?
It doesn't matter where they come from.
The joy is real.
So you are a philanthropist?
Well, hyperbole isn't the worst crime.
Men suffer more from imagining
too little than too much.
The creed of a true fraud.
Mr Bennett,
when was the last time you smiled?
Or had a good laugh?
A real laugh.
A theater critic who can't
find joy in the theater.
Now who is the fraud?
Oh, Mr. Bennett.
That word you used
to describe my show,
has a nice ring to it.
P.T. Barnum's Circus.
This way.
Don't you think there is enough
'blind trust' in my life?
Well, isn't that what makes it fun?
Keep coming. Okay.
Are you ready?
- Is it?
- It is.
Come on.
Let's go.
Push.
Helen, that's for you.
And, Caroline,
this is for you.
There is a ballet school
right down the street.
Just past your parents' house.
Don't tell me you bought this house
just to rub my parents'
noses in your success.
That was not the only reason.
This is the life I promised you.
Shall we?
Phin...
It's beautiful, but we
don't need all of this.
It took me 25 years, but...
Welcome home,
Charity Barnum.
- Hello there!
- Barnum is in.
Hey, sweetie, who is that
young man over there?
That is Philip Carlyle.
A bit of a scandal, they say.
- His last play was a hit in London.
- Play?
Pay good money to
watch people stand around and talk for
two hours, and they call me a con man.
Ew. What's that smell?
Do you smell that?
- Ew, something does smell.
- I know what it is. Peanuts.
I can see it right now.
"Youngest prima ballerina in the
history of the City ballet."
- I'm quitting.
- What? Why would you quit?
I started too late.
I will never catch up.
Caroline, you were the
best dancer on that stage.
What? Do you think
I can't spot talent?
Ballet takes years of hard work.
It's not like the circus.
You can't just fake it.
She can't quit. No.
No, I mean... She doesn't.
She just feels out of place
with the other girls.
Well, I should certainly hope so.
I have never seen so many
little prima Donnas in my life.
Yes, but those prima Donnas are the most
important thing in the
world to her right now.
She'll learn to ignore
them, just like I did.
She shouldn't have to.
New York society will never accept us.
If they did,
they'd have to stop judging...
and actually do
something with their lives.
This isn't about me.
Oh... So it's different than
everything else then?
I just want her to be proud
of who she is, of her family.
She is proud.
We don't have to be the Carlyle's.
Mr. Carlyle.
You produced this play?
Yes I do, indeed.
Refunds are available
at front box office.
- P.T. Barnum.
- From the circus?
Yes. You've been?
God, no. But I've
seen the crowds.
People leave your show happier
than when they came in.
Which is much more than
I can say from my play.
And yet, you have no
trouble selling tickets.
That's because I'm selling virtue.
Can I buy you a drink?
I want to go after
the carriage straight.
Present legitimate acts,
expand our appeal...
go after the snobs.
If you only knew how suffocating they are.
So come join our circus.
You clearly have a flair
for show business.
Teach me how to appeal
to the highbrows.
Are you serious?
Mr. Barnum, I can not just run off
enter into circus.
Why not? Sounds thrilling isn't it?
Lets just say that I find
it much more comfortable...
- admiring your show from afar.
- Comfort, the enemy of progress.
Do you understand that
just associating with you
could cost me my inheritance.
I thought it'd cost you more than that.
You would be risking everything.
But, on the other hand, well,
you just might find
yourself a free man.
♪ Right here, right now ♪
♪ I put the offer out. ♪
♪ I don't want to chase you down ♪
♪ I know you see it. ♪
♪ You run with me. ♪
♪ And I can cut you free. ♪
♪ Out of the drudgery ♪
♪ and walls you keep in. ♪
♪ So trade that typical ♪
♪ for something colorful. ♪
♪ And if it's crazy, ♪
♪ live a little crazy. ♪
♪ You can play it sensible, ♪
♪ a king of conventional. ♪
♪ Or you can risk it all and see. ♪
♪ Don't you wanna get away from ♪
♪ same old part you gotta play. ♪
♪ 'Cause I got what you need. ♪
♪ So come with me ♪
♪ and take the ride. ♪
♪ It'll take you to the other side. ♪
♪ 'Cause you can do like you do ♪
♪ Or you can do like me. ♪
♪ Stay in the cage, or you'll ♪
♪ finally take the key. ♪
♪ Oh, damn! Suddenly ♪
♪ you're free to fly. ♪
♪ It'll take you to the other side. ♪
♪ Okay, my friend, you ♪
♪ want to cut me in. ♪
♪ Well I hate to tell you, ♪
♪ but it just won't happen. ♪
♪ So thanks, but no. ♪
♪ I think I'm good to go. ♪
♪ 'Cause I quite enjoy the ♪
♪ life you say I'm trapped in. ♪
♪ Now I admire you, and ♪
♪ that whole show you do. ♪
♪ You're onto something, ♪
♪ really it's something. ♪
♪ But I live among the swells, and ♪
♪ we don't pick up peanut shells. ♪
♪ I'll have to leave that up to you. ♪
♪ Don't you know that I'm okay with ♪
♪ this uptown part I get to play. ♪
♪ 'Cause I got what I need and I ♪
♪ don't want to take the ride ♪
♪ I don't need to see the other side. ♪
♪ So go and do like you do. ♪
♪ I'm good to do like me. ♪
♪ Ain't in a cage, so I don't ♪
♪ need to take the key. ♪
♪ Oh, damn! Can't you ♪
♪ see I'm doing fine? ♪
♪ I don't need to see the other side. ♪
♪ Now is this really how you ♪
♪ like to spend your days? ♪
♪ Whiskey and misery, ♪
♪ and parties and plays. ♪
♪ If I were mixed up with you, ♪
♪ I'd be the talk of the town. ♪
♪ Disgraced and disowned, ♪
♪ another one of the clowns. ♪
♪ But you would finally live a ♪
♪ little, finally laugh a little. ♪
♪ Just let me give you the freedom ♪
♪ to dream and it'll wake you up ♪
♪ and cure your aching. ♪
♪ Take your walls and ♪
♪ start 'em breaking. ♪
♪ Now that's a deal that ♪
♪ seems worth taking. ♪
♪ But I guess I'll ♪
♪ leave that up to you. ♪
♪ Well it's intriguing, but ♪
♪ to go would cost me greatly. ♪
♪ So what percentage of the ♪
♪ show would I be taking? ♪
♪ Fair enough, you'd want a ♪
♪ piece of all the action. ♪
♪ I'd give you seven, we could ♪
♪ shake and make it happen. ♪
♪ I wasn't born this morning, ♪
♪ eighteen would be just fine. ♪
♪ Why not just go ahead and ♪
♪ ask for nickels on the dime? ♪
♪ - 15. ♪
♪ - I'm doing eight. ♪
♪ - 12. ♪
♪ - maybe nine ♪
♪ 10. ♪
Sir, it looks like you
have yourself a junior partner.
What I have is an
overcompensated apprentice.
♪ Don't you wanna get away to a ♪
♪ whole new part you're gonna play. ♪
♪ 'Cause I got what you need, so ♪
♪ come with me and take the ride. ♪
♪ to the other side. ♪
♪ So if you do like I do ♪
♪ So if you do like me. ♪
♪ Forget the cage, 'cause we ♪
♪ know how to make the key. ♪
♪ Oh, damn! Suddenly ♪
♪ we're free to fly. ♪
♪ We're going to the other side. ♪
♪ So if you do like I do. ♪
♪ To the other side. ♪
♪ So if you do like me. ♪
♪ 'Cause if we do ♪
♪ we're going to the other side. ♪
Who is that?
Hey. No one is buying hats back here.
Get out front, go.
WD, Anne, I want to introduce my
newest hire, Mr Philip Carlyle.
- It's a pleasure to meet you.
- Yeah, pleasure.
And what is your act, Mr. Carlyle?
I don't have an act.
Everyone has got an act.
- Mr. Barnum.
- Yeah?
You better come see this.
Philip, keep up.
- A bit of nasty element.
- They're always is, isn't it?
Nothing draws a crowd
crying like a crowd.
Go home you freaks.
"Shame of the city".
"The protests amend
Mr. Barnum's reputation..."
"as a previewer of the
offensive and indecent."
"Offensive and indecent."
Mr. Bennett, I'm blushing.
No, I'm blushing.
What do you care what Bennett thinks?
- He's a prick.
- And a snob.
Yeah, all the snobs in the
New York are reading me.
Does their thinking for them.
What ever happened to the
thriving of controversy?
Yeah, well...
Look, hey..
- Do you have any thoughts on this?
- Philip.
- As a matter of fact, I do.
- Helen, come on.
"The master of the Household,
has it in the command of the Queen...
To invite Mr. Phineas T
Barnum and his theatrical
troop to a reception at
Buckingham Palace."
- The Queen Victoria? Is this real?
- I had to pull a few strings.
If you want society to accept you,
you may as well start
at the very very top.
Are we all invited?
I guess I'll just have to tell
the queen either all of us go
or none of us will.
The Queen of England.
Can't get much better than that.
- Why aren't we in tails?
- We are the entertainment.
I don't see you in a costume.
Your Majesty, Mr Phineas
T Barnum and his...
Oddities from America.
Is that real?
Your Majesty,
may I present Mr Barnum.
The honor is mine, Mr. Barnum.
And I've heard all about
your little colonel
from my friends in America.
General, ma'am.
You are even smaller
than I imagined.
Well, you are not exactly reaching
the top self yourself sweetheart.
Ah, that went well.
- Your Majesty.
- Philip.
Miss Jenny Lind.
She is really luminous.
- Who is that?
- The opera singer.
Singer, huh?
She is the most famous
performer in all of Europe.
She has sold out La Scala
a dozen times.
Not to mention
the French Opera.
Striking.
- What are you doing?
- Following you...
so you can introduce
me to Miss Lind.
- Introduce you?
- Yeah.
I don't know her.
Everybody knows her.
You just said so yourself.
Yeah, exactly. You don't just
walk up to someone right now.
Why not? We are presentable.
She is a person.
Miss Lind.
My name is Phillip Carlyle.
And this extraordinary
gentleman next to me...
Phineas Taylor Barnum.
The pleasure is mine.
Of course, you are the American.
I believe I might have heard of you.
Oh well, If you've heard of
me all the way over here,
I must have been doing
something right.
That, or something very wrong.
In the world of publicity there
is hardly any difference.
I believe those are the words
of a scoundrel, Mr Barnum.
A showman, Miss Lind, just a showman.
The best on my side of the Atlantic.
- If you just say so yourself.
- I do, but I don't have to.
Oh, no, no.
He is one of the best.
That's very kind of you.
Miss Lind, let me get to the point.
I would like to bring you to New York.
And if you agree...
I will make you the most famous singer
not in Europe but in the entire world.
And have you heard me sing?
- Absolutely.
- No, I haven't.
But like mine, your
reputation precedes you...
and well, I trust your reputation
more than my own taste, so...
I have never been to America.
You will sing in the grandest theater...
with the finest orchestra in the
greatest city on earth.
"Jenny Lind".
"One night only." Or maybe two.
And at 20% at the gate, it will
be a queen's ransom for your..
I gave most of my
earnings to charity, Mr Barnum...
to orphans and widows.
"Voice of a nightingale,
Heart of an Angel."
That's brilliant. I mean the press
will go crazy with that story.
That's not a story.
May I ask you something,
Mr. Barnum?
Anything.
Why me?
People come to my show for the
pleasure of being hoodwinked.
Just once, I would love to
give them something real.
Miss Lind.
Everyone is here. Look at this.
Even the Winthrops.
- Are you happy?
- I will be, if this works.
Oh, God, I hope she can sing.
- What's taking her so long?
- They are still taking their seats.
Speaking of which. Tom and Lettie,
the others, they just arrived.
- What?
- Where should I put them? Your box?
- That box? No, that's pretty visible.
- Visible?
The acoustics are actually
better in the standing room.
That's where they should be.
- Miss Lind is ready now.
- OK. Thank you. Thank God.
This is so beautiful.
- Isn't that beautiful?
- Yes.
I love it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for your patience.
I recently had the privilege of
hearing the most divine voice...
- I've ever heard.
- Suddenly he's a connoisseur.
Now, I know that sounds
like Barnum humbug...
but I have a 100 bottles of
good champagne on ice that says
that this is not just
another sideshow novelty.
May I present, the Swedish Nightingale...
Miss Jenny Lind.
♪ I'm trying to hold to my breath ♪
♪ let it stay that way. ♪
♪ Can't let this moment end. ♪
♪ You set off a dream with me. ♪
♪ Getting louder now. ♪
♪ Can you hear it echoing? ♪
♪ Take my hand. ♪
♪ Will you share this with me? ♪
♪ 'Cause darling without you. ♪
♪ All the shine of a thousand spotlights. ♪
♪ All the stars we steal ♪
♪ from the night sky ♪
♪ will never be enough ♪
♪ never be enough. ♪
♪ Towers of gold are still too little. ♪
♪ These hands could hold the world ♪
♪ but it will never be enough ♪
♪ never be enough ♪
♪ for me! ♪
♪ never, never, ♪
♪ never for me. ♪
♪ never enough, ♪
♪ for me, for me ♪
♪ for me. ♪
♪ All the shine of a ♪
♪ thousand spotlights. ♪
♪ All the stars we steal ♪
♪ from the night sky ♪
♪ will never be enough ♪
♪ never be enough. ♪
♪ Towers of gold are still too little. ♪
♪ These hands could hold the world ♪
♪ but it will never be enough ♪
♪ never be enough ♪
♪ for me ♪
♪ never never ♪
♪ never for me ♪
♪ for me ♪
♪ never enough ♪
♪ never, never ♪
♪ never enough for me ♪
♪ for me, for me ♪
♪ for me. ♪
Bravo.
- Bravo.
- Lind.
Superb.
Bravo.
Awesome.
Jenny, this is my wife
Charity and our girls.
Of course, and I've heard
so much about you.
And your father tells me
you are a fan of the ballet.
- Yes, I'm studying ballet.
- Oh, are you?
- Of course I am.
- Of course she is.
- And what about you, Helen?
- You look like a princess, ma'am.
I have to admit, Barnum,
she is remarkable.
Enough to bring joy to the
most joyless critic, isn't she?
And in the hands of a real
previewer of the art...
she could be something
in this country.
Shame she's fallen in with you.
You really are better on the page,
Mr Banner. How does that is to believe.
Oh, Mr. Barnum? I would
love to meet Miss Lind.
And you will meet miss Lind
if you just give me a moment...
- Phineas.
- Yes.
You've done well.
Thank you.
Allow me to introduce you.
Excuse me, Jenny.
I would like you to meet Charity's parents.
- Mr and Mrs Hallett.
- Ah, pleasure.
- How do you do? Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Mother.
- Hello dear.
- Are these...
- Yes, yes, those are your granddaughters.
- Phineas, not here.
- Not here?
You are afraid that
I'm gonna embarrass your
parents in front of their
fancy friends?
I really don't think
that I have that power.
An insignificant man like me...
was clearly destined
to lead an insignificant life.
All that fortune and still
just a tailor's boy.
Get out.
Well, Phineas...
I believe that I told
you that free champagne
is a recipe for disaster.
Charity.
Now would everyone please
raise their glasses?
To Mr Barnum, who showed
once and for all...
that a man's station is limited
only by his imagination.
- To Barnum.
- Thank you.
To Mr Barnum.
Thank you.
It's hard to understand wealth and
privileges when you're born into it.
I sometimes don't feel
like I belong here.
You?
I was born out of wedlock
and that brought
shame upon my family.
And life always manages
to remind me
that I don't deserve
a place in this world.
And that leaves a hole that
no ovation can ever fill.
Mr. Phineas.
- Lord, that lady can sing.
- I know.
Thinks she likes a man in uniform?
I'm sure she does.
What are you doing here?
You got a show in an hour, OK?
That's enough time for us to have
at least three drinks, right? Come on.
- No no. Lettie.
- What?
It's very crowder in here, okay?
And I can't have you mingling.
Who's gonna pay admission
if you are out there for
all the world to see.
- Have a great show.
- Wait...
Ladies and gentlemen, a toast.
Jenny, America may not know it
yet, but they are going to love you.
To Miss Lind.
♪ I am not a stranger to the dark. ♪
♪ "Hide away," they say. ♪
♪ "'Cause we don't want your broken parts" ♪
♪ I've learned to be ♪
♪ ashamed of all my scars. ♪
♪ "Run away," they say ♪
♪ "No one will love you as you are." ♪
♪ But I won't let them ♪
♪ break me down to dust ♪
♪ I know that there's a place for us. ♪
♪ For we are glorious. ♪
♪ When the sharpest words ♪
♪ wanna cut me down. ♪
♪ I'm gonna send a flood, ♪
♪ gonna drown them out. ♪
♪ I am brave, I am bruised ♪
♪ I am who I'm meant to be ♪
♪ this is me. ♪
♪ Look out 'cause here I come. ♪
♪ And I'm marching on ♪
♪ to the beat I drum. ♪
♪ I'm not scared to be seen ♪
♪ I make no apologies, ♪
♪ this is me. ♪
What are they doing here?
♪ Another round of bullets hits my skin. ♪
♪ Well, fire away. ♪
♪ 'Cause today, ♪
♪ I won't let the shame sink in. ♪
♪ We are bursting through the barricades ♪
♪ and reaching for the sun, ♪
♪ we are warriors. ♪
♪ Yeah, that's what we've become. ♪
♪ Won't let them ♪
♪ break me down to dust. ♪
♪ - I know that there's a place for us. ♪
- Freaks, go home.
♪ For we are glorious. ♪
♪ When the sharpest words ♪
♪ wanna cut me down. ♪
♪ Gonna send a flood, ♪
♪ gonna drown them out. ♪
♪ I am brave, I am bruised ♪
♪ I am who I'm meant to be, ♪
♪ this is me. ♪
♪ Look out 'cause here I come. ♪
♪ And I'm marching on ♪
♪ to the beat I drum. ♪
♪ I'm not scared to be seen. ♪
♪ I make no apologies. ♪
♪ This is me ♪
♪ This is me. ♪
♪ And I know that ♪
♪ I deserve your love. ♪
♪ There's nothing I'm not worthy of. ♪
♪ When the sharpest words ♪
♪ wanna cut me down. ♪
♪ I'm gonna send a flood, ♪
♪ gonna drown them out. ♪
♪ This is brave, this is bruised. ♪
♪ This is who I'm meant to be, ♪
♪ this is me. ♪
♪ Look out 'cause here I come. ♪
♪ And I'm marching on to the beat I drum. ♪
♪ Marching on, marching, ♪
♪ marching on. ♪
♪ I'm not scared to be seen. ♪
♪ I make no apologies. ♪
♪ This is me. ♪
♪ When the sharpest words ♪
♪ wanna cut me down. ♪
♪ I'm gonna send a flood, ♪
♪ gonna drown them out ♪
♪ this is me. ♪
Why can't you just put
more shows in New York?
Why do you need t
tour the country?
Why did Napoleon
march on Russia?
Napoleon was defeated.
Napoleon didn't have a 60 piece orchestra.
A 60 piece orchestra.
Just get the cheapest musicians you can,
you watch that.
We still have to aboard them.
Get married ones. They can share a bunk.
O'Malley, that's Caroline's piggy bank.
Costumes sets? Fireworks?
Inside theaters?
That's genius.
No. These are the most famous
theaters in the country.
- They make you buy their seats in advance.
- Yeah, yeah. I took out a loan.
And we have to pay Jenny?
It was a large loan, okay?
You're not gonna see a penny of
profit until your 40th show.
41st actually.
You're risking everything
you've built here.
How do you think I build it?
We'll have plenty of profits
to go around after this.
- P. T?
- What?
Your attention has been
divided long enough.
Our gate is down, we have
more protesters every day.
You just need to get
people to come back.
"If you haven't been to
Barnum museum lately...
You have not been to
the Barnum Museum."
The come to see you.
Your crazy ideas, your
new acts, the unusual.
Then have you show them your smile.
That would be unusual.
Keep rehearsing.
Just make it very clear that I expect
them to afford you all the
deference you deserve...
And that they should
be nice to you anyway.
Ain't that a sight for sore eyes?
- He couldn't even say hello.
- Or goodbye.
He is going on tour.
Sorry guys.
Pull yourself together, Carlyle.
Don't you have somewhere to be?
Anne Wheeler.
Mr. Barnum said he
left a ticket for me.
I'm sorry.
- I believe this one supposed to be one.
- No, there's meant to be two.
Wasn't sure you'd come if I asked.
Five minutes to curtains.
I've always wanted to
go to the theater.
Phillip, is that you?
Mother. Father.
This is Anne Wheeler.
Phillip, have you no shame?
To associate yourself with that
Barnum business is one thing...
but parading around with that elf.
Anne.
How dare you speak
to her like that?
- You forget your place, Phillip.
- My place?
Mother, if this is my place, then
I don't wanna be a part of it.
Anne.
They are small minded people.
- Why do you care what they say?
- It's not just them.
Never had somebody look at you
the way your parents looked at me.
The way everyone would look at us.
♪ You know I want you. ♪
♪ It's not a secret I try to hide. ♪
♪ I know you want me. ♪
♪ So don't keep saying our hands are tied. ♪
♪ You claim it's not in the cards. ♪
♪ And fate is pulling you miles away. ♪
♪ And out of reach from me. ♪
♪ But you're here in my heart. ♪
♪ So who can stop me if I decide ♪
♪ that you are my destiny? ♪
♪ What if we rewrite the stars? ♪
♪ Say you were made to be mine. ♪
♪ Nothing could keep us apart. ♪
♪ You'd be the one ♪
♪ I was meant to find. ♪
♪ It's up to you, ♪
♪ and it's up to me. ♪
♪ No one can say ♪
♪ what we get to be. ♪
♪ So why don't we ♪
♪ rewrite the stars? ♪
♪ Maybe the world could be ours, ♪
♪ tonight. ♪
♪ You think it's easy? ♪
♪ You think I don't want to run to you. ♪
♪ But there are mountains. ♪
♪ And there are doors that ♪
♪ we can't walk through. ♪
♪ I know you're wondering why. ♪
♪ Because we're able to be ♪
♪ Just you and me ♪
♪ within these walls. ♪
♪ But when we go outside, ♪
♪ you're gonna wake up and see that ♪
♪ that it was hopeless after all. ♪
♪ No one can rewrite the stars. ♪
♪ How can you say ♪
♪ you'll be mine? ♪
♪ Everything keeps us apart. ♪
♪ And I'm not the one ♪
♪ you were meant to find. ♪
♪ It's not up to you, ♪
♪ it's not up to me. ♪
♪ When everyone tells us what we can be. ♪
♪ How can we rewrite the stars? ♪
♪ Say that the world can be ours, ♪
♪ tonight. ♪
♪ All I want is to fly with you. ♪
♪ All I want is to fall with you. ♪
♪ So just give me all of you. ♪
♪ It feels impossible ♪
♪ It's not impossible. ♪
♪ Is it impossible? ♪
♪ See that it's possible. ♪
♪ How do we rewrite the stars? ♪
♪ Say you were made to be mine? ♪
♪ Nothing can keep us apart. ♪
♪ Cause you are the one ♪
♪ I was meant to find. ♪
♪ It's up to you, ♪
♪ and it's up to me. ♪
♪ No one can say ♪
♪ what we get to be. ♪
♪ And why don't we ♪
♪ rewrite the stars? ♪
♪ Changing the world to be ours. ♪
♪ You know I want you. ♪
♪ It's not a secret I try to hide. ♪
♪ But I can't have you. ♪
♪ We're bound to break and ♪
♪ my hands are tied. ♪
First it was buying a house on
the same street as my parents.
Then meeting the queen.
Then bringing Jenny Lind, and
my father the other night.
When will it ever be
enough for you?
I am doing this for
Caroline and Helen.
Look around you.
They have everything.
- You don't understand.
- I do.
No. You don't understand!
How could you?
My father was treated like dirt.
I was treated like dirt.
My children will not be.
You don't need everyone
to love you, Phin.
Just a few good people.
I know that.
- Thank you.
- Sir.
No. Daddy.
Daddy.
Daddy, no. Wait.
- Daddy.
- Go.
Wait, Daddy.
♪ Some people long for a life ♪
♪ that is simple and planned. ♪
♪ Tied with a ribbon. ♪
♪ Some people won't sail the sea ♪
♪ 'cause they're safer on land. ♪
♪ To follow what's written. ♪
♪ But I'd follow you ♪
♪ to the great unknown. ♪
♪ Off to a world ♪
♪ we call our own. ♪
♪ Mountains and valleys, and all ♪
♪ that will come in between ♪
♪ desert and ocean ♪
♪ you pull me in ♪
♪ and together ♪
♪ we're lost in a dream. ♪
♪ Always in motion ♪
♪ so I risk it all ♪
♪ just to be with you. ♪
♪ And I risk it all ♪
♪ for this life we choose. ♪
♪ Hand in my hand ♪
♪ and you promised to never let go. ♪
♪ We're walking the tightrope. ♪
♪ High in the sky. ♪
♪ We can see the whole world down below. ♪
♪ We're walking the tightrope. ♪
♪ Never sure, ♪
♪ will you catch me if I should fall? ♪
♪ Well, it's all an adventure ♪
♪ that comes with a breathtaking view. ♪
♪ Walking the tightrope ♪
♪ with you ♪
♪ with you. ♪
"It is as though we've learned
for the first time..."
what singing really is.
Miss Lind deserves our nation's highest
esteem and lavish ovations.
- I mean...
- The world at our feet.
Well, Mr. Barnum.
This...
is...
to making dreams come true.
Thank you, Jenny.
It's two hours to curtains.
I've given you the world, haven't I?
I, I should go.
I have become a distraction.
I'm sorry, Jenny.
- You should finish your tour without me.
- What? You're leaving?
- The itinerary is well in hand.
- So that's it.
What do you mean?
I'm just another your acts.
- Jenny.
- I'm done.
Jenny, Jenny, please.
You have to finish the tour.
- Must I?
- It will ruin me.
When you're careless
with other people Mr Barnum...
you bring ruin upon yourself.
- I have risked everything.
- Well, so did I.
And seems we've both lost.
♪  All the stars we steal ♪
♪ from the night sky.  ♪
♪ Will never be enough ♪
♪ never be enough. ♪
♪ Towers of gold are still too little. ♪
♪ These hands could hold the world ♪
♪ but it will never be enough ♪
♪ never be enough. ♪
Thank you.
What was that?
That was goodbye.
Thank you very much for coming.
- Say your fancy neighbors.
- What a beautiful show.
Who enjoyed yourselves? You?
Tell everyone how much fun you
had at the circus.
New acts every night.
Hey, ringmaster.
Gentlemen, I am gonna
have to ask you to leave.
This is our town, son.
We think you should leave,
you and your freaks.
And yours spooks.
Sir.
I will only ask once more.
Then what, boy?
Attack.
Daddy.
- Daddy. Daddy!
- Girls.
You have grown so much.
What made you decide
to come back early?
I missed you.
- That sounds lawful.
- Fire.
- Out of the way. Fire!
- Hurry, it's coming from the circus.
Girls, stay with me.
Come, quickly.
Everyone! Stay close.
Phillip, is everyone out?
Is everyone okay?
The animals?
We set them free.
What else could we do?
- WD, where is Anne?
- Where is Anne?
No, Phillip.
No. Stop.
You can not go inside.
Keep pumping.
- WD.
- There she is.
- Phillip.
- Daddy.
- No dad.
No.
Stay back, please.
Daddy.
Stretcher, stretcher.
He has taken a lot of smoke.
He's still breathing.
Let's get him on.
Up.
What if we rewrite the stars?
Say you were meant to be mine?
Nothing can keep us apart
you are the one I was meant to find.
Here we go.
Come on, straight ahead.
If you had come to gloat
I wouldn't.
They caught the thugs
who started the fire.
I thought you'd like to know.
I never liked your show.
But I always thought the people did.
They do.
Mind you, I wouldn't call it art.
Of course not.
But...
Putting folks of all kinds on stage.
All colors, shapes, sizes.
Presenting them as equals.
Another critic might have even called it
'a celebration of humanity'.
I would have liked that.
Well, I hope you'll rebuild.
Thank god for Jenny's tour.
We can borrow off the profits.
We'll be fine.
You don't know?
I'm sorry.
Charity?
Oh God, Charity.
- I am...
- I don't wanna talk to you.
- Nothing happened.
- Ouch, nothing happened.
It's on the cover of
every paper in New York.
Because she orchestrated the photo.
I am not in love with her.
Of course you're not.
Not with her, not with me,
not with anyone.
Just you and your show.
What are you doing?
I'm going home.
This is your home.
The bank..
They are evicting us.
Why didn't you ask me before?
I would have said yes.
I never minded the risk,
but we always did it together.
Figured you'd end up here.
Feeling sorry for yourself?
Folks if you have come to get paid,
the money's gone. All of it.
- Nothing left to give...
- Shut up, Barnum.
You just don't get it.
Our own mothers were ashamed of us.
Hid us our whole lives.
Then you pull us out of the shadows.
And now you are giving upon us too.
Maybe you are fraud.
Maybe it was just about making a buck.
But you gave us a real family.
And the circus...
That was our home.
We want our home back.
♪ I saw the sun begin to dim. ♪
♪ And felt that winter wind ♪
♪ blow cold. ♪
♪ A man learns who is there for him. ♪
♪ When the glitter fades ♪
♪ and the walls won't hold. ♪
♪ 'Cause from then, rubble ♪
♪ one remains. ♪
♪ Can only be once true. ♪
♪ If all was lost. ♪
♪ There's more I gained. ♪
♪ Cause it led me back ♪
♪ to you. ♪
♪ I drank champagne ♪
♪ with kings and queens ♪
♪ the politicians praised my name. ♪
♪ But those are someone else's dreams. ♪
♪ The pitfalls of the man I became. ♪
♪ For years and years ♪
♪ I chased their cheers. ♪
♪ The crazy speed of always needing more. ♪
♪ But when I stop and see you here ♪
♪ I remember who all this was for ♪
♪ and from now on. ♪
♪ These eyes will not be ♪
♪ blinded by the lights. ♪
♪ From now on. ♪
♪ What's waited till tomorrow ♪
♪ starts tonight ♪
♪ it starts tonight. ♪
♪ And let this promise in me start. ♪
♪ Like an anthem in my heart ♪
♪ from now on ♪
♪ from now on. ♪
♪ And we will come back home ♪
♪ home again. ♪
♪ From now on we will come back home. ♪
♪ And we will come back home ♪
♪ home again. ♪
♪ And we will come back home. ♪
♪ And we will come back home ♪
♪ home again. ♪
♪ And we will come back home. ♪
♪ And we will come back home ♪
♪ home again. ♪
♪ from now on ♪
♪ and we will come home again ♪
♪ home again ♪
♪ from now on. ♪
♪ These eyes will not be ♪
♪ blinded by the lights! ♪
♪ From now on! ♪
♪ What's waited till tomorrow ♪
♪ starts tonight! ♪
♪ It starts tonight. ♪
♪ Let this promise in me start. ♪
♪ Like an anthem in my heart ♪
♪ from now on ♪
♪ from now on and we ♪
♪ will come home again. ♪
♪ And we will come back home ♪
♪ home again. ♪
You are here.
♪ From now on ♪
♪ from now on ♪
♪ home again ♪
♪ home again. ♪
- Caroline.
- He's here.
I would like to see my wife.
She's not here.
She's at the beach.
I have brought hardships
on you and our family.
You warned me...
and I wouldn't listen.
I just wanted...
I wanted to be more than I was.
I never wanted anything but
the man I fell in love with.
♪ Let this promise in me start. ♪
♪ Like an anthem in my heart ♪
♪ however big ♪
♪ however small ♪
♪ from now on. ♪
From now on.
- The bank said no?
- Emphatically. And repeatedly.
I don't think there is a
bank left in this country...
I can fool into loaning
me more money, so...
I'm really sorry to disappoint you all.
Don't worry, Barnum.
We've gotten used to it by now.
You know, Barnum...
when I first met you...
I had an inheritance, claim...
and an invitation to every party in town.
And now thanks to you.
All that's gone.
All that's left is this friendship, love
and work that I adore.
You brought joy into my life.
- Into all our lives.
- Yeah.
I need a bank who takes joy as collateral.
They may not...
But I will.
I own 10% of the show.
Knowing who I was working for...
I had the good sense to take my cut weekly.
Phillip, I can't let you gamble it on me...
Sure you can.
Don't turn sensible on us now.
Partners.
Fifty fifty.
The only this is...
I don't know how we're
gonna afford a building.
Right.
We don't need a building.
Real estate in Manhattan
is a terrible investment.
I can get a land down by the
docks for almost nothing.
All we need is a tent.
♪ This is the most beautiful show. ♪
♪ - Come on. ♪
♪ Colossal we calm these ♪
♪ renegades in the rain ♪
♪ where the lost get found in ♪
♪ the crown of the circus cage. ♪
♪ Don't fight it, it's coming ♪
♪ for you, running at ya. ♪
♪ It's only this moment, don't ♪
♪ care what comes after. ♪
♪ It's blinding outside and ♪
♪ I think that you know. ♪
♪ Just surrender 'cause you're ♪
♪ calling and you wanna go. ♪
♪ Where it's covered in ♪
♪ all the colored lights. ♪
♪ Where the runaways are running the night. ♪
♪ Impossible comes true, ♪
♪ intoxicating you. ♪
♪ Oh, this is the greatest show. ♪
♪ We light it up, ♪
♪ we won't come down. ♪
♪ And the sun can't stop us now. ♪
♪ Watching it come true, ♪
♪ it's taking over you. ♪
♪ Oh, this is the greatest show. ♪
♪ It's everything you ever want. ♪
♪ It's everything you ever need. ♪
♪ And it's here right in front of you. ♪
♪ This is where you wanna be. ♪
♪ It's everything you ever want. ♪
♪ It's everything you ever need. ♪
♪ And it's here right in front of you. ♪
♪ This is where you wanna be. ♪
♪ When it's covered in all the colored lights. ♪
♪ Where the runaways are running the night. ♪
♪ Impossible comes true, ♪
♪ - This is for you. ♪
♪ it's taking over you ♪
♪ Oh, this is the greatest show. ♪
♪ - What are you going to do? ♪
♪ - Watching my girls grow up. ♪
♪ The show must go on ♪
♪ - We won't come down. ♪
♪ And the sun can't stop us now. ♪
♪ Watching it come true, ♪
♪ it's taking over you. ♪
♪ This is the greatest show. ♪
♪ When it's covered ♪
♪ in all the colored lights. ♪
♪ Where the runaways are running the night. ♪
♪ Impossible comes true, ♪
♪ it's taking over you. ♪
♪ Oh, this is the greatest show ♪
♪ we won't come down. ♪
♪ And the walls can't stop us now. ♪
♪ I'm watching it come true, ♪
♪ it's taking over you. ♪
♪ Oh, this is the greatest show. ♪
♪ 'Cause everything you want ♪
♪ is right in front of you. ♪
♪ And you see the ♪
♪ impossible is coming true. ♪
♪ And the walls can't stop us now, yeah. ♪
♪ This is the greatest show. ♪
♪ This is the greatest show! ♪
Daddy.
Hey, girls.
Hey. Out of the way.
♪ This is the greatest show. ♪
♪ It's everything you ever want. ♪
♪ It's everything you ever need. ♪
♪ And it's here right in front of you. ♪
Fixed by MoviesLover..